

# Luca Vigotti

# Front-End Developer

# **PROFILE**

Multilingual professional from Italy with a passion for Front End Development.

I discovered this passion when I worked as an IT Recruitment Consultant. When I started researching the industry I tried coding to better understand the roles I was recruiting for. Doing this I realized coding is what I want to do. I have lived on every continent but Antarctica and I have worked with people from all over the world. Now my journey has me as a developer in Japan.

#### **EDUCATION**

Web Development Bootcamp

LeWagon Tokyo

**BA** in Psychology

Vancouver Island University

Japanese Language Student

Yoshida Institute of Japanese Language

01/2023 - 03/2023 Tokyo, Japan

09/2015 - 06/2019 Nanaimo, BC, Canada

10/2019 - 09/2020 Tokyo, Japan

#### **PROJECTS**

# Kotoback 🔗

- Users can upload epub ebooks which are automatically translated and turned into flashcards. I primarily worked on the Front End. I was in charge of all the UI and UX aspects of the app.
- HTML5, CSS, Javascript, Ruby on Rails

# Haunted Tours ₽

- Spooky tour ideas based on the Airbnb model which allows you to host and/or book a tour.
- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails

## **SKILLS**

KLAR K.K

HTML5 | CSS | JavaScript | Ruby | Ruby on Rails | Figma

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**English Teacher** 

05/2020 - 12/2022

06/2021 - 02/2022

Tokyo, Japan

Tokyo, Japan

Saiei Internation, Progress English Camp • Over 80% of the students was able to pass the TOEIC/EIKEN test.

**Recruitment Consultant** 

• Searched for the best talents in IT and Digital Marketing.

• Assisted candidates and clients finding the best match for them.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Italian: Native | English: Native level | Japanese: Limited working proficiency